Anthony Rosman

Frontend web developer

♥ Venezuela ☑ anthonyrosman20@gmail.com ↓ +584249253164 in anthonyrosman ♠ D3press3dd

⊕ D3press3dd
⑤ D3press3dd
□

PROFILE

Software Engineer and Front-end developer freelance graduated from Venezuela with **5+ years of experience** building and creating user-friendly websites and web applications. 2 years **with React** js, I spend my time on personal projects and learning more about Front-end and how to improve my skills.

Always eager to adapt and take on new challenges!



Frontend (Html,Css,Css3,Sass,Bootstrap,Styled Components, Modules,BEM,Javascript (ES6+),Typescript,Git,Github, Npm, Gulp ,React, React Router, Redux)

EDUCATION

Master computer engineering, Ludovico Silva University

Feb 2010 – Jun 2016 | Monagas, Venezuela

Bachelor of science, Unare III institute

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Web developer React, FREELANCER.COM

present

Creation and maintenance of software on the freelance.com platform with a good reputation and experience, more than 100 websites created under quality standards

Frontend Web Developer, CROING

Mar 2019 - Dec 2020

Participated in various company projects such as creating modules for web promotions for companies such as Sprite, Adidas and Reebok, located in Argentina and Chile.

Frontend Developer, EZIA

Feb 2018 - Feb 2019

Participate in various projects of the company performing tasks such as code documentation and front-end development.

Frontend Web Developer, PHARMACOLOGY UNIVERSITY | E-COMMERCE

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

- Analysis, Design and Development of an Information System under Web environment, Database Manager in PostgreSQL, development environment in: HTML, PHP 5, JavaScript, JQuery, Documentation, Training and Implementation of the System.



English (B1)

Spanish